ANDRÉ LISBOA

andrelisboa.co



PROFILE

Hello! I'm André Lisboa, a UI/UX Designer with over 9 years of experience working on digital products. Since 2015, I've collaborated with various teams to create solutions that meet user needs while maintaining strong visual and functional design.

Also, I've been teaching UI/UX at Alura Online Courses It's the biggest online course platform in Brazil and I've launched 19 courses, reaching over 50,000 students since 2018. These courses cover key topics such as UI Design with Figma, building design systems, creating microinteractions, and prototyping, helping students develop practical skills for real-world applications.

CONTACT

al.andrelisboa90@gmail.com

+55 (21) 99385-3311

São Paulo - SP

SKILLS

UI/UX Design; Design Systems; Visual design; Responsive design; User testing; Handoff for devs

EDUCATION



Visual Design

PUC-Rio

2011-2015

LANGUAGES



Portuguese

Native



English

Fluent



Spanish

Can communicate



Learning

EXPERIENCE



Senior Product Designer

Since 2023

As a Product Designer at Valid since 2023, I've been building end-to-end government applications while also leading the development and maintenance of the company's design system.

UI/UX Teacher

Alura Online Courses

Since 2018

Since 2018, I have been teaching UI design at the Alura course school. I have launched 19 courses with themes that explore the world of UI and UX.

Senior UI Designer

Fluency Academy

2022-2023

Between 2022 and 2023, I worked at Fluency as a Senior UI Designer. My goal was to evolve the brand's products with UI design.

UI Designer

Afinz Bank

2021-2022

My main objective with the company was the construction of the design system, along with the creation of flows and functionalities.

UI/UX Designer

Super Revendedores

2018-2020

At Super Revendedores, I was responsible for the entire creation and evolution of the platform in terms of design. I was responsible for creating new journeys and flows for the system, which existed on the website, iOS, and Android.

qx3 UI/UX Designer

QX3

2016-2018

My first experience as a graduated UI designer, I was responsible for the evolution of the Sunset corporate events application.